AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records 5478
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XXIII: National Rules and Working Conditions Agreements Between Employees Represented by the Railway Employees Department of the AFL and Carriers Under the Provisions of the Transportation Act of 1920 - Correspondence, Etc., 1920-1934
  - International and Great Northern Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    Code No. MC-48-14-74; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 2, 1922
  - Norfolk and Western Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    Code No. MC-121-14-75; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 16, 1922
  - Kansas City Southern Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    Code No. MC-81-14-76; Apr. 27, 1922 - Jun. 3, 1922
  - Mississippi Central Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 16)
    Code No. MC-102-14-77; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 1, 1922
  - Bangor and Aroostook Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 17)
    Code No. MC-13-14-78; Apr. 27, 1922 - Jun. 2, 1922
  - Gulf Coast Lines Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 18)
    Code No. MC-60-14-79; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 25, 1922
  - System Federation No. 86 - Ontario Northland Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 19)
    Code No. MC-60-14-80; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 4, 1922
  - Chicago River and Indiana Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 20)
    Code No. MC-207-14-81; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 5, 1922
  - K.&M. Railroad Machinists - Middleport Lodge 676, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 21)
    Code No. MC-80-14-82; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 8, 1922
  - Michigan Central Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 22)
    Code No. MC-94-14-83; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 7, 1922
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 23)
    Code No. MC-94-14-84; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 8, 1922
  - Hocking Valley Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 24)
    Code No. MC-69-14-85; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 26, 1922
  - Central Vermont Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 25)
    Code No. MC-21-14-86; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 5, 1922
  - El Paso and Southwestern Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 26)
    Code No. MC-49-14-87; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 13, 1922
  - Southern Railway, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 27)
    Code No. MC-49-14-88; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 8, 1922
  - Trinity and Brazos Valley Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 28)
    Code No. MC-171-14-89; Apr. 27, 1922 - Jun. 19, 1922
  - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 29)
    Code No. MC-26-14-90; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 10, 1922
  - A.B.&A. Railway, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 30)
    Code No. MC-4-14-91; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 9, 1922
  - Peoria and Pekin Union Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 31)
    Code No. MC-132-14-92; Mar. 19, 1922 - May 22, 1922
  - Northwestern Pacific Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 32)
    Code No. MC-123-14-93; Apr. 27, 1922 - Jun. 12, 1922
  - Lehigh and New England Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 33)
    Code No. MC-92-14-94; Apr. 11, 1922 - Jun. 5, 1922
  - Western Pacific Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 34)
    Code No. MC-189-14-95; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 29, 1922
  - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 35)
    Code No. MC-115-14-96; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 18, 1922
  - Ft. Worth and Denver City Railway, 1922-1923 (Box 112, Folder 36)
    Code No. MC-53-14-97; May 8, 1922 - Nov. 23, 1923
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 37)
    Code No. MC-43-14-98; Apr. 27, 1922 - May 31, 1922
  - Missouri, Kansas and Texas Railway, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 38)
    Code No. MC-100-14-99; May 24, 1922 - Jun. 6, 1922
  - Louisiana and Northwest Railroad, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 39)
    Code No. MC-488-14-100; Jul. 31
  - Special Circular to the General Chairmen on Railroads where workers have returned to work under the Baltimore Agreement, etc., 1922-1925 (Box 112, Folder 40)
    Code No. MC-0-14-103; Nov. 16, 1922 - Mar. 24, 1925
  - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1923 (Box 112, Folder 41)
    Code No. MC-9-14-115; Mar. 21, 1923 - Apr. 25, 1923
  - Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railroad, 1923 (Box 112, Folder 42)
    Code No. MC-47-14-118; May 3-4
  - Correspondence with Reference to Baltimore Agreement Commission, 1922-1929 (Box 112, Folder 43)
    Code No. 14-101-1; Jul. 23, 1922 - Apr. 15, 1929
  - Correspondence with Reference to Baltimore Agreement Commission, 1922-1923 (Box 112, Folder 44)
    Code No. 14-101-2; Sept. 19, 1922 - Apr. 11, 1933
  - Correspondence re Circular Letter of January 19, 1922, 1921-1922 (Box 112, Folder 45)
    Code No. 14A-1; Sept. 19, 1921 - Feb. 3, 1922
  - Results of meeting of Executive Council Mechanical Sec. and Executive Board of Divisions 1, 2, and 3 of R.E.D. in re Rules governing working conditions, 1919- 1921 (Box 112, Folder 46)
    Code No. 14A-1; Jan. 21, 1919 - Sept. 18, 1921
  - U.S. Railroad Labor Board - Correspondence, 1921-1922 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    Code No. 14A; Nov. 15, 1921 - Apr. 4, 1922
  - Report of Crew Files, 1921-1922 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    Code No. MC-0-14A-1 1/2; Aug. 26, 1921 - Feb. 2, 1922
  - American Railway Express Co. - Shop Employees - Negotiating rules and working conditions, 1920-1921 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    Code No. MC-17- 14A-11; Jun. 7, 1920 - Nov. 8, 1921
  - Abilene and Southern Railroad, 1921 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    Code No. MC-458-14A-213; Aug. 19, 1921 - Nov. 29, 1921
  - Akron, Canton, Youngstown Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    Code No. MC-436-14A-207; Apr. 16, 1921 - Jun. 30, 1922
  - Alabama Great Southern Railroad, 1921 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    Code No. MC-158-14A-31; Aug. 1, 1921 - Aug. 12, 1921
  - Alabama and Vicksburg Railway, 1921 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    Sept. 23
  - Alabama, Tennessee and Northern Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    Code No. MC-368-14A-127; May 21, 1921 - Mar. 10, 1922
  - Alton and Southern Railroad, 1921 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    Code No. MC-217-14A-117; May 21, 1921 - Nov. 14, 1921
  - American Refrigerator Transit Company, 1921-1922 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    Code No. MC-204-14A-152; Jun. 2, 1921 - May 5, 1922
  - Ann Arbor Railroad, 1921 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    Code No. MC-5-14A-6; Apr. 22, 1921 - Oct. 29, 1921
  - Apalachicola Northern Railroad, 1921-1923 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    Code No. MC-335-14A-128; May 17, 1921 - Nov. 15, 1923
  - Arizona Eastern Railroad, 1921 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    Code No. MC-3-14A-141; May 7, 1921 - Aug. 6, 1921
  - Atchison and Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    Code No. MC-1-14A-23; May 4, 1921 - Feb. 1, 1922
  - Atlanta and West Point Railroad and Western Alabama Railroad, 1921 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    Code No. MC-193-14A-140; May 26, 1921 - Aug. 30, 1921
  - Atlanta, Birmingham and Atlantic Railroad, 1921 (Box 113, Folder 16)
    Code No. MC-4-14A-208; May 29, 1921 - Aug. 5, 1921
  - Atlanta Joint Terminal Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 113, Folder 17)
    Code No. MC-7-14A-184; Jun. 17, 1921 - Mar. 4, 1922
  - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1921 (Box 113, Folder 18)
    Code No. MC-2-14A-96; May 19, 1921 - Sept. 18, 1921
  - Atlantic and St. Lawrence Railroad, 1921 (Box 113, Folder 19)
    Sept. 22
  - Baltimore, Chesapeake and Atlantic Railway, 1921 (Box 113, Folder 20)
    Code No. MC-424-14A-97; May 17, 1921 - Sept. 6, 1921
  - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 113, Folder 21)
    Code No. MC-9-14A-43; May 6, 1921 - Jun. 12, 1922
  - Baltimore and Ohio Chicago Terminal Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    Code No. MC-117-14A-202; May 21, 1921 - Aug. 15, 1921
  - Bangor and Aroostook Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    Code No. MC-13-14A-147; May 26, 1921 - Oct. 26, 1921
  - Barr and Chelsea Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    Aug. 10
  - Bath and Hammondsport Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    Aug 6-26
  - Battle Creek Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    Code No. MC-427-14A-211; Aug. 1
  - Beaumont Wharf and Terminal Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Beaumont, Sour Lake and Western Railway, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    Code No. MC-60-14A-70; Sept. 23, 1921
  - Bellington and Northern Railway, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    Code No. MC-26-14A-49; Aug. 8, 1921 - Aug. 29, 1921
  - Belt Railroad of Chicago, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    Code No. MC-14-14A-204; May 7, 1921 - Aug. 3, 1921
  - Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    Code No. MC-16-14A-82; May 16, 1921 - Aug. 6, 1921
  - Bethlehem Steel and P.B. and N.E. Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    Code No. MC-12-14A-93; Jul. 7, 1921 - Nov. 7, 1921
  - Boston and Albany Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    Code No. MC-11-14A-78; May 10, 1921 - Aug. 6, 1921
  - Boston and Maine Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    Code No. MC-10-14A-16; Apr. 27, 1921 - Oct. 26, 1921
  - Boston Terminal Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    Code No. MC-419-14A-212; Aug. 1, 1921 - Oct. 1, 1921
  - Buffalo, Rochester, and Pittsburgh Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    Code No. MC-8-14A-54; May 8, 1921 - Nov. 11, 1921
  - Buffalo, Rochester, and Pittsburgh Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Buffalo and Susquehanna Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    Code No. MC-15-14A-177; Jun. 11, 1921 - Jul. 13, 1922
  - Buffalo and Susquehanna Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Camas Prairie Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    Code No. MC-428-14A-29; Apr. 30, 1921 - Aug. 1, 1921
  - Carolina, Clinchfield and Ohio Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 20)
    Code No. MC-427-14A-17; May 4, 1921 - Oct. 1, 1921
  - Central of Georgia Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 21)
    Code No. MC-23-14A-121; May 30, 1921 - Aug. 1, 1921
  - Central of New England Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 22)
    Code No. MC-109-14A-131; May 26, 1921 - Aug. 6, 1921
  - Central Railroad of New Jersey, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 23)
    Code No. MC-19-14A-143; May 11, 1921 - Dec. 10, 1921
  - Central Vermont Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 24)
    Code No. MC-21-14A-15; May 3, 1921 - Jun. 6, 1922
  - Central Vermont Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - Central Vermont Transportation Co., 1921 (Box 114, Folder 26)
    Code No. 21-14A; Aug. 10, 1921 - Aug. 15, 1921
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, 1921-1923 (Box 114, Folder 27)
    Code No. MC-29-14A-67; May 13, 1921 - Jan. 30, 1923
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, 1921-1923 (Box 114, Folder 28)
  - Champaign and St. Lawrence Railroad, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 29)
  - Charleston and Western Carolina Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 30)
    Code No. MC-215-14A-186; Jun. 22, 1921 - Jun. 21, 1922
  - Charleston and Western Carolina Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 31)
  - Chicago and Alton Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 32)
    Code No. MC-30-14A-75; May 12, 1921 - Mar. 3, 1922
  - Chicago and Northwestern Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 33)
    Code No. MC-25-14A-64; May 5, 1921 - Mar. 3, 1922
  - Chicago and Northwestern Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 34)
  - Chicago, Indianapolis and Louisville Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 35)
    Code No. MC-24-14A-2; Apr. 22, 1921 - Feb. 20, 1922
  - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 36)
    Code No. MC-26-14A-104; May 20, 1921 - May 9, 1922
  - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 37)
  - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 38)
    Code No. MC-27-14A-49; May 7, 1921 - Feb. 10, 1922
  - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 39)
  - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 40)
  - Canadian Pacific Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 41)
    Code No. MC-218-14A-214; Aug. 1, 1921 - Jun. 9, 1922
  - Central Indiana Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 114, Folder 42)
    Code No. MC-130-14A-7; Apr. 25, 1921 - Jan. 20, 1922
  - Chicago Junction Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    Code No. MC-207-14A-203; May 10, 1921 - Aug. 6, 1921
  - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    Code No. MC-33-14A-52; May 4, 1921 - Oct. 14, 1921
  - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Car Interchange Bureau, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    Code No. MC-196-14A-161; May 12, 1921 - Sept. 29, 1921
  - Chicago, Detroit, Canada Grand Trunk Junction Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Great Western Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    Code No. MC-22-14A-69; Mar. 26, 1921 - Feb. 11, 1922
  - Chicago Great Western Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    Code No. MC-214-14A-205; Apr. 12, 1921 - Aug. 9, 1921
  - Chicago, St. Paul and Minneapolis and Omaha Railway, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    Code No. MC-34-14A-35; Apr. 27, 1921 - Dec. 30, 1921
  - Chicago, St. Paul and Minneapolis and Omaha Railway, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    Code No. MC-37-14A-71; May 4, 1921 - Jul. 14, 1922
  - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Chicago, Milwaukee and Gary Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    Code No. MC-224-14A-13; Apr. 29, 1921 - Nov. 30, 1921
  - Chicago, Peoria and St. Louis Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 115, Folder 16)
    Code No. MC-206-14A-87; May 8, 1921 - Mar. 21, 1922
  - Chicago, Terre Haute and Southeastern Railway, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    Code No. MC-35-14A-90; May 4, 1921 - Sept. 22, 1921
  - Cincinnati, Saginaw and Mackinaw Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Colorado and Southern Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 19)
    Code No. MC-20-14A-8; Apr. 30, 1921 - Nov. 17, 1921
  - Copper Range Railroad, 1921-1923 (Box 115, Folder 20)
    Code No. MC-347-14A-40; Apr. 30, 1921 - Mar. 19, 1923
  - Cumberland and Pennsylvania Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    Code No. MC-112-14A-87; May 13, 1921 - Aug. 5, 1921
  - Coal and Coke Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 22)
    Aug. 10, 1921 - Oct. 7, 1921
  - Chicago, Kalamazoo and Saginaw Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 23)
    Code No. MC-450-14A-197; Jul. 8, 1921 - Oct. 31, 1921
  - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railway, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 24)
    Code No. MC-6-14A-22; Apr. 21, 1921 - Sept. 24, 1921
  - Cincinnati, Burnside and Cumberland River Railway, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 25)
  - Chesterfield and Lancaster Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 26)
    Aug. 3, 1921 - Oct. 13, 1921
  - Cincinnati, New Orleans & Texas Pacific Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 27)
    Code No. MC-158-14A-031; Aug. 1, 1921 - Aug. 12, 1921
  - Denver and Salt Lake Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 28)
    Code No. MC-42-14A-167; Jun. 3, 1921 - Sept. 7, 1921
  - Detroit, Grand Haven and Milwaukee Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 29)
  - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 115, Folder 30)
    Code No. MC-40-14A-162; May 26, 1921 - Jun. 7, 1922
  - Detroit, Toledo and Ironton Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 31)
    Code No. MC-41-14A-136; May 26, 1921 - Nov. 9, 1921
  - Duluth, South Shore and Atlantic Railway, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 32)
    Code No. MC-350-14A-216; Jun. 30, 1921 - Sept. 21, 1921
  - Dallas Union Terminal and Depot Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 33)
    Code No. MC-453-14A-206; Aug. 3, 1921 - Sept. 27, 1921
  - Davenport, Rock Island and Northwestern Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 115, Folder 34)
    Code No. MC-444-14A-192; Jul. 1, 1921 - Jul. 13, 1922
  - Dayton and Union Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 35)
    Aug. 10 - Oct. 7
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 36)
    Code No. MC-43-14A-50; May 6, 1921 - Sept. 22, 1921
  - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 37)
    Code No. MC-39-14A-160; May 31, 1921 - Aug. 6, 1921
  - Denver and Rio Grande Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 115, Folder 38)
    Code No. MC-38-14A-124; May 20, 1921 - Feb. 8, 1922
  - Denver Union Terminal Company, 1921 (Box 115, Folder 39)
    Code No. MC-425-14A-126; May 22, 1921 - Aug. 25, 1921
  - Detroit and Mackinac Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 115, Folder 40)
    Code No. MC-185-14A-171; Apr. 28, 1921 - Feb. 18, 1922
  - Duluth and Iron Range Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 115, Folder 41)
    Code No. MC-45-14A-60; May 7, 1921 - Jun. 21, 1922
  - Duluth, Missabe and Northern Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    Code No. MC-46-14A-59; May 7, 1921 - Jun. 21, 1922
  - Duluth Union Depot and Transfer Company, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    Code No. MC-451-14A-199; Jul. 18, 1921 - Aug. 19, 1921
  - Duluth, Winnipeg and Pacific Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    Code No. MC-223-14A-62; May 7, 1921 - Aug. 19, 1921
  - Dennison, Pacific Suburban Railway, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    Aug. 3, 1921 - Aug. 12, 1921
  - East St. Louis and Suburban Railway, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    Code No. MC-438-14A-153; May 26, 1921 - Aug. 11, 1921
  - East St. Louis Junction Railway, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    Code No. MC-50-14A-151; May 31, 1921 - Sept. 24, 1921
  - El Paso and Southwestern Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    Code No. MC-49-14A-65; May 10, 1921 - Oct. 13, 1921
  - El Paso and Southwestern Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Erie Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    Code No. MC-48-14A-66; May 17, 1921 - Oct. 31, 1921
  - Erie Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Code No. MC-47-14A-81; May 17, 1921 - Dec. 17, 1921
  - El Paso Terminal Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    Code No. MC-208-14A-198; Jul. 18, 1921 - Sept. 22, 1921
  - Florida East Coast Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    Code No. MC-51-14A-55; May 9, 1921 - Nov. 25, 1921
  - Fort Dodge, Des Moines and Southern Railroad, 1922 (Box 116, Folder 14)
    Code No. MC-363-14A-223; Feb. 18, 1922 - May 29, 1922
  - Fort Worth and Denver City Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 15)
    Code No. MC-53-14A-25; May 2, 1921 - Aug. 16, 1921
  - Fort Worth and Denver City Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Fort Smith and Western Railroad, 1921-1939 (Box 116, Folder 17)
    Code No. MC-53-14A-51; Apr. 28, 1921 - Jul. 14, 1939
  - Fort Worth Belt Railway, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Galveston Wharf Company, 1921-1922 (Box 116, Folder 19)
    Code No. MC-470-14A-222; Aug. 4, 1921 - Feb. 16, 1922
  - Galveston, Houston and Henderson Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 20)
    Code No. MC-437-14A-145; May 26, 1921 - Sept. 22, 1921
  - Great Northern Railway, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 21)
    Code No. MC-67-14A-28; Apr. 30, 1921 - Dec. 19, 1921
  - Green Bay and Western Railway, 1921-1923 (Box 116, Folder 22)
    Code No. MC-65-14A-79; May 17, 1921 - May 3, 1923
  - Gulf and Ship Island Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 23)
    Code No. MC-203-14A-144; May 25, 1921 - Sept. 28, 1921
  - Gulf, Mobile and Northern Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 24)
    Code No. MC-61-14A-108; May 18, 1921 - Aug. 19, 1921
  - Georgia, Florida and Alabama Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 25)
    Code No. MC-59-14A-168; Jun. 4, 1921 - Aug. 29, 1921
  - Gallatin Valley Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 26)
    Aug. 8
  - Galveston, Harrisburg and San Antonio Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 27)
    Code No. MC-63-14A-130; May 22, 1921 - Aug. 6, 1921
  - Georgia, Southern and Florida Railway, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 28)
  - Grand Trunk System Lines in U.S., 1921 (Box 116, Folder 29)
    Code No. MC-54-14A-63; Mar. 28, 1921 - Sept. 24, 1921
  - Grand Trunk Western Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 30)
  - Grand Canyon Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 31)
  - Georgia Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 32)
    Code No. MC-62-14A-189; Jun. 28, 1921 - Aug. 27, 1921
  - Hocking Valley Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 33)
    Code No. MC-69-14A-95; May 4, 1921 - Sept. 22, 1921
  - Long Island Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 116, Folder 34)
    Code No. MC-88-14A-101; May 17, 1921 - Feb. 8, 1922
  - Lackawanna and Montrose Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 35)
    Aug. 3, 1921 - Aug. 10, 1921
  - Lewiston and Auburn Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 36)
  - Lake Erie and Western Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 37)
    Code No. MC-87-14A-187; Jun. 27, 1921 - Sept. 20, 1921
  - Gulf Coast Lines Railroad, 1921 (Box 116, Folder 38)
    Code No. MC-434-14A-194; Jun. 30, 1921 - Oct. 26, 1921
  - Gulf Coast Lines Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 116, Folder 39)
    Code No. MC-60-14A-70; May 6, 1921 - Jun. 22, 1922
  - Gulf Coast Lines Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 116, Folder 40)
  - Harriman and Northeastern Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Huntington and Broad Top Mountain Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    Jun. 6, 1921 - Jun. 29, 1921
  - Houston Belt and Terminal Railway, 1921-1922 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    Code No. MC-72-14A-99; May 14, 1921 - Sept. 26, 1922
  - Hudson and Manhattan Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    Code No. MC-346-14A-155; May 25, 1921 - Oct. 13, 1921
  - Huntington and Broad Top Mountain Railroad and Coal Company, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    Code No. MC-73-14A-98; May 17, 1921 - Nov. 25, 1921
  - International and Great Northern Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    Code No. MC-77-14A-47; Apr. 11, 1921 - Nov. 25, 1921
  - International and Great Northern Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Illinois Central Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    Code No. MC-74-14A-10; Apr. 29, 1921 - Jan. 31, 1922
  - Illinois Terminal Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    Code No. MC-351-14A-105; May 12, 1921 - Oct. 10, 1921
  - Indianapolis Union Railway Company, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    Code No. MC-241-14A-134; Jun. 29, 1921 - Aug. 16, 1921
  - Jacksonville Terminal Company, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    Code No. MC-78-14A-56; May 7, 1921 - Aug. 15, 1921
  - Joplin Union Depot Company, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    Code No. MC-445-14A-172; Jun. 6, 1921 - Aug. 18, 1921
  - Kansas City, Mexico and Orient of Texas Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    Code No. MC-84-14A-123; May 20, 1921 - Aug. 6, 1921
  - Kansas City Southern Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    Code No. MC-81-14A-80; May 16, 1921 - Dec. 10, 1921
  - Kansas City Terminal Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 15)
    Code No. MC-79-14A-122; Apr. 20, 1921 - Oct. 26, 1921
  - Kansas City, Clinton and Springfield Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    Code No. MC-455-14A-209; Aug. 4, 1921 - Sept. 29, 1921
  - Kansas, Oklahoma & Gulf Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 17)
    Code No. MC-101-14B-94; May 16, 1921 - Aug. 2, 1921
  - Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 18)
    Code No. MC-82-14A-107; May 18, 1921 - Aug. 6, 1921
  - Kansas South Western Railway, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Kanawha and Michigan Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 20)
    Code No. MC-80-14A-114; May 9, 1921 - Mar. 24, 1922
  - Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer Railway, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 21)
    Code No. MC-392-14A-37; May 7, 1921 - Aug. 3, 1921
  - Lake Superior and Ishpeming Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 117, Folder 22)
    Code No. MC-430-14A-61; May 7, 1921 - Mar. 10, 1922
  - Louisiana and Arkansas Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 23)
    Code No. MC-90-14A-48; May 9, 1921 - Nov. 22, 1921
  - Lehigh and Hudson River Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 24)
    Code No. MC-111-14A-106; May 18, 1921 - Nov. 14, 1921
  - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 25)
    Code No. MC-86-14A-102; May 17, 1921 - Sept. 27, 1921
  - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - Litchfield and Madison Railway, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 27)
    Code No. MC-440-14A-149; May 31, 1921 - Sept. 23, 1921
  - Lehigh and New England Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 28)
    Code No. MC-92-14A-185; Jun. 27, 1921 - Aug. 17, 1921
  - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 117, Folder 29)
    Code No. MC-93-14A-30; May 6, 1921 - Feb. 2, 1922
  - Louisiana Railway and Navigation Company Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 30)
    Code No. MC-360-14A-157; May 27, 1921 - Sept. 28, 1921
  - Louisville, Henderson and St. Louis Railroad, 1921 (Box 117, Folder 31)
    Code No. MC-85-14A-100; May 18, 1921 - Aug. 6, 1921
  - Maine Central Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 117, Folder 32)